William Adam Stocks Junior Full Stack Developer

willstocks@me.com • +0043 6602023073 • Austria github • linkedin

Executive Summary

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python. I have 20 years experience in Customer Service and Hospitality. Also 14 years experience in Personal Security Industry. From these experiences I have acquired strong communication skills, problem solving skills, developed both leadership and valuable team-player attributes. I am eager to enter the tech industry into an exciting development team where I can continue learning and contribute to the team.

Education

March 2023 – Present Diploma in Full Stack Software Development

Code Institute - Dublin, Ireland -

(Credit Rated by University of West of Scotland)

March 2023 CCTV Licensed Operator

Leeds, UK

November 2021 LS2 Ski Instructor Course

Zell am See, Austria

February 2021 Avalanche Instructor Course

Obertauren, Austria

July 2012 Close Protection Officer

ANUBIS, Hereford, UK

September 2005–June 2009 Adventure Leisure Management, HND

Gloucestershire University, UK

Technical Skillset

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python
Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, Postgres
Frameworks: Django, jQuery, Bootstrap
Version Control: Git, Github

Portfolio projects

Luka vs Toys - Bespoke site for a 4-year-old child. Which allowed the child to play a simple rock, paper, scissors game and to give access to the child's favorite 'YouTube' channels. Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS, JavaScript. GitHub - https://stocks84.github.io/Luka_vs_Toys/

2. Sanja Savasana Retreat - E-commerce site for a Yoga Retreat in Austria. Very basic as it was the first project. Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS. GitHub - https://stocks84.github.io/Sanja-Savasana-Retreat/

Work Experience

July 2012-Present SSI Ltd (Hereford), Close Protection Officer

London, UK

- Working on your own and within Teams.
- Conflict Management.
- Time Management.
- Trustworthy.

December 2018-April 2020 Bar Owner/Landlord

Alpendorf, Austria

December 2009-April 2020 Ski Instructor/Ski Rep, Alpendorf Ski Resort

Alpendorf, Austria

- This work was only during the winter seasons.
- Managing small and large groups.
- Head ski instructor/Leadership role.
- Constant problem solving.
- Time Management.

2005-2012 Working in various Restaurants and Bars

Cheltenham, UK

- Part time work whilst studying.
- Jobs included Waiter, Barmen, and Manager roles.

Interests/Additional Information

- I am a keen reader.
- I am a keen skier and traveler.
- Fluent English, Beginner German.